

TYLER KEATON

Full Stack Developer

CONTACT

Cell: 727-277-0008

Email: work.tkeaton@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Tyler I have 8+ years experience developing using a wide variety of languages. I graduated from St. Petersburg College with an A.S. degree for Computer Programming & Analysis while maintaining a 3.8 GPA and a spot on the Deans list. Programming is more than a career to me, it's a passion/hobby I unceasingly try to improve.

MAIN INTERESTS

- iOS/Android App development
- Blockchain
- Artificial Intelligence
- Robotic Engineering
- Bluetooth Mesh
- Exercise
- Traveling
- Non-fiction Books

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

St. Petersburg College

Computer Programming and Analysis

- Deans list | 3.8 GPA
- Education Path | Open Source / C#

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Developer

Pennexx | 2019 - 2023

- Backend development (PHP, SQL, Linux, FTP, Flutter)
- Unreal Engine
- -Zoom API (HTML5/CSS3, Jquery, PHP, SQL, python)

Full Stack Developer

Nutech | 2017 - 2019

- Custom CRM: (HTML5,CSS3,Jquery,PHP,POP3,STMP,MySQL)
- iOS App: (Swift, Cocoa Pods, PHP, Ruby, MySQL)
- Website: (HTML5, CSS3, Jquery)
- Network Manager

Self / Independent Projects | 2021 - 2022

- Blockchain / Solidity development
- iOS / Swift app development
- Chat Gpt A.I / TTS / STT

CERTIFICATES

- Responsive Web Design
- Programming Specialist

LANGUAGES

- Flutter / Dart (iOS, Android, Chrome, MacOS) Applications | 4yrs.
- Swift | 3yrs.
- HTML5 / CSS3 | 8yrs.
- JQuery / JS | 8yrs.
- Python / Ruby | 4yrs.
- PHP / SQL | 8yrs.
- Unreal Engine | 1yr.
- C#/OOP | 8yrs.
- C++ | 2yrs.
- Linux/Unix | 6yrs.